PERSONAL DATA



Name:	Denis Kachurovskyi
Date of Birth:	12.07.1994
Location:	Ukraine, Zaporizhzhia
Mobile:	+38 (096) 245-21-41
E-mail:	kachurovskyi.d@gmail.com
GitHub:	https://github.com/KachurovskyiD
LinkedIn:	www.linkedin.com/in/kachurovskyid
Telegram:	https://t.me/KachurovskyiD

OBJECTIVE

Desired Position: Front-end developer

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATION

I'm studying and practicing in web development from the end of 2018.

Since 2020, I have been working on the freelance platform Weblancer.

I also have experience working in a commercial company.

For a year and a half, i worked as a WEB developer in the commercial company "Dedey Digital".

Participated in the development of projects in the team, both new and existing projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5 (Responsive / Adaptive, Mobile First);
- CSS3 / Flexbox / Grid / SASS (SCSS) / LESS / Bootstrap 4;
- JavaScript (ES6+);
- React.js / Redux / React router / React hooks / Next.js / Formik / React Transition Group and etc.;
- AJAX / fetch / Axios;
- REST API;
- Styled Components, CSS Modules, BEM;
- UI frameworks (React-bootstrap, Material UI);
- Animations (AOS, animate, GSAP).

TOOLS

- Git, Bitbucket, Jira;
- Gulp, npm;
- Photoshop, Figma, Avocode, VS Code.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

- Communication with the customer;
- Projects and features development;
- Tasks review and estimations;
- Team management;
- SEO promotion;
- Marketing research.

LANGUAGES

- English Pre-Intermediate;
- Russian Native Speaker (reject);
- Ukrainian Native Speaker.

EDUCATION

 2012 - 2018 / Zaporizhzhia state engineering academy, Faculty of Economics / Economic cybernetics

SEVERAL FACTS ABOUT ME

I prefer a healthy lifestyle.

In my free time I'm doing self-development activities.

I'm free of the bad habits.

I can find the optimal way from difficult situation by myself in short time period.

I have an experience in teaching other people by programming skills.

I have experience in team management.

I can attribute to my positive qualities: punctuality, diligence, responsibility, creativity, sociability, ability to learn and adapt to new conditions.

COURSES AND CERTIFICATES

Course name:	Brain Academy Course "Basic programming"
Issued:	Brain Academy Zaporozhye
Years of study:	04/2019 - 06/2019
Certificate license number:	1296

Course name:	Brain Academy Course "Front-end development"
Issued:	Brain Academy Zaporozhye
Years of study:	10/2019 - 04/2020
Certificate license number:	1692

1

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

"POST FINANCE"	
Company:	"POST FINANCE"
Company Location:	Ukraine, Kyiv
Personal Location:	Ukraine, Zaporizhzhia
Duration:	05/2017 - 10/2020
Description:	Promotion and control of financial services provided to the leader of the company's logistics transportation "NOVA POSHTA"
Position:	Specialist operator, head of department, chief accountant
Responsibilities:	 Control of work quality Team management Business correspondence Analytics and performance monitoring

"Dedey Digital"	
Company:	"Dedey Digital"
Company Location:	Ukraine, Vinnytsya
Personal Location:	Ukraine, Zaporizhzhia
Duration:	03/2021 - 08/2022
Position:	WEB-developer
Responsibilities:	Website developmentSupport of existing projectsElimination of existing errors

1